My name's Conan Edogawa!
اسمي إيدوغاوا كونان
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a drug that shrunk him.
أُجبر طالب الثانوية شينتشي على تجرّع عقار قلّص جسده
If the organization learned that Shinichi and Conan were the same person,
إن عرفت المنظمة أنّ شينتشي وكونان ،هما نفس الشخص
everyone close to me would be in danger!
!فسيقع جميع من حولي في خطر
The only one who knows the truth is Professor Agasa!
!البروفسور آغاسا وحده من يعرف الحقيقة
I hide my identity yet again today, in which there is only one truth!
أُخفي هويتي، والحقيقة واحدة دوماً !اليوم كذلك
There is no such thing as "the perfect crime."
لا وجود للجريمة الكاملة
I'm sorry to say this, but your crime is as clear as daylight.
يؤسفني قول هذا، لكن جريمتك بوضوح الشمس
You've made three very basic mistakes!
ارتكبت ثلاثة أخطاء أساسية
Mistake #1: Cans scattered around the waste bin in an unnatural fashion.
الأوّل: العلب المبعثرة حول حاوية النفايات بشكل لا طبيعي
The number of cans is proof enough that there's something inside the bin.
عددها كفيلٌ بإثبات أنّ هناك شيء داخل الحاوية
Mistake #2: The ice cream bar you were just eating is lying nearby.
الثاني: الآيس كريم الذي كنت تأكله قبل قليل مرميّ في الخارج
Yes. You were in a rush to hide,
،أجل، اختبأت في عجلة من أمرك
so you dropped it on the ground, half-eaten.
لذا أسقطته على الأرض، نصف مأكول
Mistake #3: The most incriminating evidence of all...
...الثالث: أكثر الأدلّة إدانة
...is that I can see your big butt inside the waste bin, Genta-kun!
هو أنّ بإمكاني رؤية مؤخرتك الكبيرة !بين العلب في الحاوية يا غينتا-كن
You talk too much, you know?!
!أنتَ كثير الكلام
Arrested
مُعتقل
Ayumi-chan! I found Genta too! Come back!
!أيومي-تشان، وجدتُ غينتا أيضاً! ارجعي
Already?!
بهذه السرعة؟
It's no fun when you're it-- the game always ends right away!
...اللعبة ليست مسليّة عندما تكون الملاحق !أقصد، المتحرّي. دائماً ما تنتهي بسرعة
It's no fun for me either!
الأمر ليس مسلياً لي أيضاً
A high school student playing detective games in the park...
طالب في الثانوية يلعب لعبة المتحرّيين في الحديقة
These badges are so awesome!
!هذه الشارات رائعة
They say "Detective Boys" since we're the Junior Detective Club!
!مكتوب عليها "ديتيكتف بويز"، أي فتيان التحرّي
We're the only grade school students in the world with badges like these!
نحن طلّاب الابتدائية الوحيدون في العالم !الذين يملكون شارات كهذه
Yeah, huh?
صـ-صحيح
There are tiny transceivers built inside!
توجد قطع إرسال واستقبال صغيرة داخلها
You can communicate over long distances
يمكنكم التواصل على مسافات بعيدة
by using the dial on the back to change frequencies!
باستعمال القرص في الخلف لتغيير التردد
It's perfect for kids' games, but I'd rather not have to play myself...
إنّها جيدة لألعاب الأطفال، لكنّي أفضّل ألّا يقحموني
If they hadn't come over to invite me to play,
،لو لم يأتوا لدعوتي للعب
I would've gone with Ran to Teitan University's school festival!
لذهبت مع ران لمهرجان جامعة تيتان
Don't you worry! I'll have plenty of fun with the college girls for you!
!لا تقلق! سأستمتع كثيراً مع فتيات الجامعة بدلاً عنك
Okay! This time I'll be the detective and you guys'll be the criminals!
!حسنٌ! سأكون المتحرّي هذه المرة وأنتم المجرمون
I have to be a criminal again?!
عليّ أن أكون المجرم مجدداً؟
We only need one detective! Now get going!
!يكفي مُتحرٍّ واحد! اذهبا
Whatever.
تبّاً
One, two, three...
...واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة
I love Hide-and-Go-Seek!
!أُحب الغميّضة كثيراً
Hurry, Conan-kun!
!أسرع يا كونان
I can't believe I keep going along with this...
يجرّونني معهم باستمرار
What happens if this keeps up and I turn stupid?!
ماذا لو تحوّلت لأحمق هكذا؟
Upsy daisy. Sorry!
سأصعد، المعذرة
99, 100!
!تسع وتسعون، مئة
Here I come! Time to show you all the skill of Genta Kojima-sama,
...حسنٌ، سأريكم مهارة قائد فرقة فتيان التحرّي
leader of the Junior Detective Club!
!كوجيما غينتا-ساما
Genta's looking hard!
يبحث غينتا بجد
"Multiple girls kidnapped and murdered."
"سلسلة جرائم اختطاف وقتل فتيات"
They still haven't caught those guys yet?!
لم يمسكوا بالمجرم بعد؟
Scary, isn't it?
مخيف، صحيح؟
Ayumi-chan...
...أيومي-تشان
Cute girls are the only ones they're going after.
يستهدفون الفتيات الظريفات فقط، صحيح؟
That means I'm in huge danger, huh?
هذا يعني أنّي في خطر كبير
But I'm not worried.
لكنّي لا أشعر بالقلق
If something bad ever happened,
...إن حصل مكروه
you'd be there to protect me, wouldn't you, Conan-kun?
فستكون موجوداً لحمايتي، صحيح يا كونان-كن؟
After all, we're destined to be together!
!فقدرنا أن نكون معاً
Come on now, Ayumi-chan...
...أيومي-تشان، رويدك
Found you, Conan!
!وجدتك يا كونان
You may be good at finding people, but you sure suck at hiding!
قد تجيد إيجاد الآخرين، لكنك فاشل في الاختباء
I hate running away and hiding from people!
أنا أكره الهرب والاختباء
That's weird though, I could swear I heard Ayumi's voice too...
هذا غريب، سمعتُ صوت أيومي
Stupid! Hurry and hide!
!حمقاء! اختبئي بسرعة
Was there something there?
أكان شيء هناك؟
Just a cat!
!قطّة فقط! قطّة
Let's see... Somewhere for me to hide...
...حسناً، مكان للاختباء
What's keepin' that idiot?!
!ما الذي يؤخر ذاك الأحمق؟
Lucky!
!يا لحظّي
Found Mitsuhiko!
!وجدت ميتسوهيكو
Odd. Scientifically speaking, he shouldn't have found me.
هذا غريب، كان يُفترض ألّا يجدني علمياً
What was scientific about that?
أين العلميّ في هذا؟
Okay! That leaves just Ayumi!
!حسنٌ! بقيت أيومي فقط
That dumb Genta...
...غينتا الأحمق
How long can it possibly take him to find an ordinary little girl?!
كيف له أن يتأخر هكذا في إيجاد !فتاة صغيرة عادية؟
She is not an ordinary little girl.
ليست فتاةً صغيرة عادية
Oh, never mind...
...لا-لا تهتم
Guess I'll tune up the skateboard the professor gave me.
سأضبط لوح التزلج الذي أعطاني إيّاه البروفسور
Um, do you mind if I ask you something?
أتمانع إن سألتك شيئاً؟
How do you... How do you feel about Ayumi-chan?!
ما... ما شعورك تجاه أيومي-تشان؟
I'm asking you how you feel about her as a girl!
!أسألك عن شعورك تجاهها كفتاة؟
As just a friend!
!مـ-مجرد صديقة
Oh, really?
هكذا إذاً؟
Mitsuhiko... Don't tell me you have a crush on Ayumi-chan...
...ميتسوهيكو، أيمكن أنّك معجب
No! I'm simply asking your opinion to help me decide on my "life plan"!
كلا! سألتك عن رأيك لمساعدتي !في تحديد خطّة حياتي فقط
Life plan? You're not talking about marriage, are you?!
خطّة حياتك؟ أتقصد الزواج؟
You're so lucky! The professor makes so much stuff for you!
!يا لحظّك! يصنع لك البروفسور أشياء كثيرة
Gimme a break! Kids these days!
...يا إلهي، أطفال هذه الأيام
What took you so damn long?!
!ما الذي أخّرك هكذا؟
Come on! I already said I'm sorry!
!يكفي! اعتذرت بالفعل
We're in trouble if we don't get movin'!
!سنكون في مشكلة إلم نتحرك
Yeah.
أجل
You still haven't found Ayumi-chan?
لم تجد أيومي-تشان بعد؟
Just give up and have her come out.
استسلم واطلب منها الخروج إذاً
Yeah, right!
!مستحيل
Like I'd ever say anything that uncool in front of her...
!مُحال أن أقول شيئاً سخيفاً كهذا أمامها
Ah! So Genta likes Ayumi-chan too!
هكذا إذاً، غينتا معجب بأيومي-تشان أيضاً
After all, we're destined to be together!
!فقدرنا أن نكون معاً
What a situation I've gotten myself into...
...يا للوضع الذي وقعتُ فيه
Ayumi-chan! Can you hear me?
أيومي-تشان! أتسمعينني؟
Let's call it quits. You can come out now.
لننه اللعبة، يمكنك الخروج
That's strange.
غريب
Do you think she went home without us?
أرجعت للبيت قبلنا؟
Maybe something happened to her?!
!أيمكن أن أمراً حلّ بها؟
I'll turn the volume up...
...حسناً، سأرفع الصوت
Ayumi-chan! Ayumi-chan!
!أيومي-تشان! أيومي-تشان
Conan-kun?
كونان-كن؟
Ayumi-chan!
!أيومي-تشان
Ow!
!مؤلم
Conan-kun?!
كونان-كن؟
Where are you?!
!أين أنت الآن؟
I don't know. Somewhere dark and cramped.
لا أدري، مكان مظلم وضيّق
How did I get here?
كيف وصلت هنا؟
That sound!
...هذا الصوت
It's a car!
!إنّها سيّارة
Oh, yeah!
صحيح
I hid in the trunk of a car that was stopped in front of the park.
صعدت صندوق سيّارة كانت مركونة أمام الحديقة
But then I got sleepy...
...ثمّ شعرت بالنعاس
In front of the park?!
أمام الحديقة؟
That car?!
!تلك السيّارة؟
What's this?! Awesome!
!ما هذا؟! مذهل
Money! There's tons of it in a paper bag!
!إنّه مال! مال! الكثير منه في كيس ورقي
A million yen times 100, I bet!
!قرابة مليون ينّ ضرب مئة
A hundred million?!
!مئة مليون؟
Awesome!
!مذهل
The car must belong to someone rich!
لا بدّ أنّها سيارة رجل ثري
Why would that much money be in a paper bag?!
لمَ قد يكون هناك مبلغ كهذا في كيس ورقي؟
Is there anything else besides the money?
أيوجد شيء آخر؟
Let me see...
...حسناً
Yeah, there is. It looks like a plastic bag.
يوجد، يبدو كأنّه كيس بلاستيكي
Is it filled with grilled eel lunches?!
!أهو مملوء بأنقليس مشوي؟
Oh, look, a saw.
هذا... إنّه منشار
A saw...?
منشار؟
But what's this thing? It's slippery!
لكن ما هذا الشيء؟ إنّه زلق
Hey. You been hearin' a kid's voice come from the back?
أسمعت صوت طفلة من الخلف؟
Knock it off. There's no way that thing could talk.
أوقف هذا، من المحال أن يتكلم ذاك الشيء
Yeah, you're right.
معك حق
Is the saw the only thing inside the bag?
هل المنشار وحده داخل الكيس؟
There's also something round and wrapped in paper...
...يوجد شيء آخر ملفوف بورق
Let me see what's inside...
...دعوني أرى ما بداخله
Stop! Don't open that, Ayumi-chan!
!توقفي! لا تفتحيه يا أيومي-تشان
It's a head! A girl's head!
!رأس! إنّه رأس فتاة
A girl's head?!
!رأس فتاة؟
Don't tell me the car Ayumi-chan got in
...أيمكن أنّ السيارة التي صعدتها أيومي
belonged to those kidnappers who're killing little girls!
!هي لمجرمي اختطاف الفتيات وقتلهن؟
Hey! Something's not right!
!هناك شيءٌ غريب
Yeah, I heard it too!
!أجل! سمعتها أيضاً
Let me check out the trunk.
دعني أتفقد الصندوق
Hey, unlock it!
!افتح القفل
Right!
!أجل
Ah! So that's what we heard!
هكذا إذاً، ذاك ما سمعناه
That had me scared for a minute there!
أفزعني حقاً
Don't cry!
!لا تبكي
Don't cry, Ayumi-chan! They'll hear you if you do!
!لا تبكي يا أيومي-تشان! سيسمعونك إن فعلتِ
I know! Think of something funny!
!وجدتها! فكّري بشيءٍ مُسلٍّ
Something funny?
شيء مُسلٍّ؟
Ayumi-chan?
أيومي-تشان؟
I just remembered how Genta-kun looked like a bear
تذكرتُ كيف بدا غينتا-كن كدبّ
when he fell down the stairs the other day and got two bumps!
عندما سقط من الأدراج ذاك اليوم !وأصبح برأسه نتوئين
Girls don't make sense, even at times like this...
الفتيات لسن منطقيات حتّى في أوقات كهذه
Ayumi-chan. You can stop now.
يمكنك التوقف الآن يا أيومي-تشان
Be quiet and don't move a muscle!
!ابقي هادئة ولا تتحركي
Okay...
حسناً
I'm coming to save you!
!سآتي لإنقاذك سريعاً
Okay!
!حسناً
But how are you gonna chase them?!
لكن كيف ستلحق بهم؟
They're in a car, you know! It'll be hopeless with that skateboard!
!إنّهم في سيارة، لن تستطيع بلوح تزلج
The professor made this for me-- it's no ordinary skateboard!
!صنعه لي البروفسور، ليس لوح تزلج عاديّ
It's equipped with a high-performance turbo engine!
!إنّه مزود بمحرك نفّاث الأداء
But it's solar powered, so you can only use it when the sun is out.
لكنّه يعمل بالطاقة الشمسية، لذا لا يمكنك استعماله سوى تحت ضوء الشمس
One hour until sunset...
ساعة حتى الغروب
Are you stupid? You guys wait here!
!أأنتما أحمقان؟! انتظرا هنا
That car belongs to a couple of murderers!
!تلك سيّارة قتلة
Murder, schmurder!
!تبّاً للقتلة
I can't just sit here while Ayumi-chan is in danger!
!لا يمكنني البقاء ساكناً وأيومي-تشان في خطر
Protecting women is a man's duty!
!واجب الرجل حماية الفتاة
You're serious...
...أنتما
Alright, then!
حسناً
Ayumi-chan! Where's the car now?!
أيومي-تشان! أين السيارة الآن؟
I have no idea!
لا أدري
This car's weird, it keeps moving and then stopping!
هذه السيّارة غريبة، تتوقف وتتحرك باستمرار
Plus there are weird sounds outside...
كما أسمع أصوات غريبة في الخارج
Turn up your badge's volume, would you?
!ارفعي صوت شارتك
Okay...
حسناً
This sound...
...هذا الصوت
That's it! They're stuck in traffic because of road construction!
فهمت! إنّهم عالقون في زحام مروري بسبب أعمال إنشاء على الطريق
The only place around here where there's construction
المكان الوحيد بأعمال إنشاء في هذه المنطقة
is at the intersection on 2nd Street!
!هو التقاطع على الشارع الثاني
We can still catch them!
!لا يزال بإمكاننا اللحاق بهم
Here we go! Better hold on!
!سننطلق! تشبّثا جيداً
Right!
!أجل
Ayumi!
!أيومي
There's no reason to kill her, you know.
لكن ليس هناك داعٍ لقتلها
Her parents paid the ransom, and besides, she's just a kid...
دفع والداها الفدية، كما أنّها مجرد طفلة
You fool! She's seen our faces.
!أحمق! رأت وجهينا
We can't leave her alive! Even if she is just a kid!
!لا يمكننا تركها حيّة! حتى لو كانت طفلة
Bastards!
!الوغدان
Hang on, Ayumi! We're coming for you!
!انتظري يا أيومي! سنأتيك فوراً
Where is their car?!
أين سيّارتهم؟
Ayumi! Are you still stopping and going?!
أيومي! هل لا تزال السيارة تتوقف وتتحرك؟
Yeah. But it's not the same place as before.
أجل، لكنه ليس المكان السابق نفسه
I don't hear those weird sounds anymore,
لم أعد أسمع الأصوات الغريبة
plus the car just drove a long way!
كما أنّ السيارة قطعت خطّاً طويلاً للتو
Hold on. If they're in a traffic jam up ahead, then...
...لحظة، إن كانوا في زحام مروري أمامنا
That's it! The freeway!
!وجدته! الطريق السريع
This is bad! There's no catching them if they get on the freeway!
هذا سيّئ! لن نستطيع اللحاق بهم إن دخلوا الطريق السريع
Dammit! What do we do?!
!تبّاً! ماذا أفعل؟
There sure have been a lot of police cars passing by...
مرّت الكثير من سيارات الشرطة
Yeah, that's the fourth one...
أجل، هذه الرابعة
Inspector Megure?
المفتّش ميغوري؟
Is something going on?
أهناك أمرٌ يجري؟
...the kidnappers appear to have escaped to the city of Beika.
يبدو أنّ المختطفين فرّوا لمدينة بيكا
The authorities have formed a police cordon
شكّلت الشرطة حاجزاً
and are trying as hard as possible to arrest them.
ويبذلون قصارى جهدهم لاعتقالهم
Ayumi-chan! Have you heard any police cars?!
!أيومي-تشان! ألم تسمعي صوت سيارات شرطة؟
Yeah! About 3 of them passed by when we were stopped!
!سمعت! مرّت 3 منها عندما كنا متوقفين
There's no doubt about it! They've set up an inspection checkpoint!
!لا شكّ إذاً! وضعوا نقطة تفتيش
Probably where the roads converge right before the freeway starts--
...عند التقاء الطرق قبل الخطّ السريع غالباً
on Beika Bridge!
!على جسر بيكا
Let's go!
!حسنٌ
Hey! Beika Bridge is straight down that last street!
!جسر بيكا من الشارع السابق مباشرةً
You idiot! They wouldn't dare go through the checkpoint!
!أحمق! لن يمروا بنقطة التفتيش
They'd obviously take a side street to get out of Beika
سلكوا طريقاً جانبياً للخروج من بيكا
without going over the bridge!
!دون قطع الجسر بالتأكيد
They'll have to come down this street!
سيمرون بهذا الشارع حتماً
We're moving! The car's moving!
!نحن نتحرك! السيارة تتحرك
Bring it on! You're as good as ours!
!حسنٌ، تعالوا! سنمسك بكم
Where are they? It's already been 5 minutes...
لم يأتوا بعد، مرّت 5 دقائق
Hey! What the heck's going on, Conan?!
!ما الذي يحدث يا كونان؟
That's odd.
غريب
Ayumi-chan! Is the car stopped right now? Or is it moving?
أيومي-تشان، هل السيارة متوقفة الآن أم تتحرك؟
What's going on, Ayumi-chan?!
!ما الخطب يا أيومي-تشان؟
Say something, Ayumi!
!أجيبي يا أيومي
Did she go out of range?!
!هل خرجت عن النطاق؟
No, these things have a broadcast radius of 20 kilometers!
كلا، لهذه الأدوات مدى إرسال بعشرين كيلومتراً
There's no way they could've gone that far in 5 minutes!
!من المحال أن يقطعوا ذاك القدر في 5 دقائق
Maybe she's in a tunnel or something?!
ربما دخلوا نفقاً؟
Beika Tunnel! That must be it!
!نفق بيكا! ذلك هو حتماً
No, they'd have to pass through the inspection point and go over the bridge
كلا، عليهم المرور بنقطة التفتيش وعبور الجسر
to enter Beika Tunnel!
!لدخول نفق بيكا
Which means they must be inside a building that disrupts our signals!
مما يعني أنّهم داخل بناء يعيق الإشارة
You don't think it's their hideout, do you?!
أتقصد أنّهم في مخبئهم وما شابه؟
In that case, they're like rats in a trap!
!إنّهم محاصرون في تلك الحالة
The police'll find them eventually!
!ستجدهم الشرطة بنهاية المطاف
You idiot!
!أحمق
They'll find Ayumi-chan before they get caught!
!سيجدون أيومي-تشان قبل أن يُقبض عليهم
She's seen our faces. We can't leave her alive!
!رأت وجهينا! !لا يمكننا تركها حيّة
Even if she is just a kid!
!حتّى لو كانت طفلة
If something bad ever happened,
إن حصل مكروه
you'd be there to protect me, wouldn't you, Conan-kun?
فستكون موجوداً لحمايتي، صحيح يا كونان-كن؟
Ayumi!
!أيومي
...na... ku...
نان-كن...
Conan-kun! Where are you?!
!كونان-كن! أين أنت؟
Ayumi-chan!
!أيومي-تشان
Why wouldn't you say anything, you jerk?!
!لمَ لم تجب يا أحمق؟
Calm down, Ayumi-chan!
!اهدئي يا أيومي-تشان
They'll hear you if you yell too loud!
!سيسمعانك إن صرختِ
There's no way they would hear me!
!من المستحيل أن يسمعاني
The car's so loud that I can't hear their voices!
صوت السيّارة مرتفع جداً بحيث لا أستطيع سماع صوتهما
Do you know where you are right now?!
!أتعرفين أين أنتم الآن؟
No! There was this roaring sound and then you stopped replying to me!
!كلا، كان هناك صوت هادر ثمّ توقفت عن الإجابة عليّ
Roaring sound? So they were in the tunnel?!
!صوت هادر؟ أيمكن أنّه صوت نفق؟
But how did they pass through the checkpoint?!
!هل تجاوزا نقطة التفتيش؟ كيف؟
We'll come after you right away!
!سنلحق بك سريعاً
Just keep quiet and wait for us!
!ابقي هادئة وانتظرينا
Come on, faster!
!بسرعة! بسرعة
The skateboard'll stop soon if we don't hurry!
!سيتوقف اللوح قريباً إلم نسرع
Conan-kun! It sounds like the car's in some sort of shop now!
!كونان-كن! يبدو أنّ السيارة دخلت محلّاً الآن
Shop?!
محلّ؟
I heard someone say, "Welcome," and this weird sound just started!
سمعت أحدهم يقول "مرحباً"، كما أنّ صوتاً غريباً قد بدأ
Sound?!
صوت؟
A gas station! Which one?!
!محطّة وقود! أيّ واحدة؟
Ayumi-chan! Let me hear what's going on outside!
!أيومي-تشان! دعيني أسمع ما يجري في الخارج
Okay.
حسناً
We're currently giving away Masked Yaiba towels and T-shirts...
نوزع الآن مناشف وقمصان يايبا المقنع
We don't need any! We're in a hurry!
!لا نحتاجها! نحن في عجلة
The only gas station you can get Masked Yaiba stuff
محطّة الوقود الوحيدة التي توفر بضائع يايبا المقنع
is Yotsubishi Gas, which we just passed!
!هي محطّة يوتسوبيشي التي تجاوزناها للتو
I finally found them!
!وجدتكم أخيراً
What was that sound, Conan-kun?!
!ما كان ذاك الصوت يا كونان-كن؟
Ayumi-chan's definitely in the trunk of that car!
!أيومي-تشان داخل صندوق تلك السيارة بالفعل
As is the girl's head and the money!
!كما رأس الفتاة والمال
They're the ones kidnapping and killing little girls!
!إنّهما مرتكبا جرائم اختطاف وقتل الفتيات الصغيرات
Hey, did you hear anything strange just now?
ألم تسمع صوتاً غريباً؟
It's just some kids playing pranks!
!إنّهم أطفال، عبث أطفال فقط
What's going on?
ما الذي يجري؟
What's going on, Ayumi-chan?!
!ماذا هناك يا أيومي-تشان؟
Ayumi-chan! Respond! Ayumi-chan!
!أيومي-تشان! أجيبي! أيومي-تشان
Hey, something's definitely strange!
!هناك أمرٌ غريب حتماً
It's probably just a stray cat. No need to get worked up!
قطّة ضالة لا أكثر غالباً، لا داعي للقلق
Bastards! There's no escape now!
!أوغاد! لن تهربوا الآن
Huh?!
!لـ-لحظة
What's going on?!
ما الخطب؟
They're getting away!
!إنهم يبتعدون
Oh no! There's not enough solar power!
!كلا! لا طاقة شمسية كافية
We have to do something before we stop altogether!
!علينا فعل شيء قبل أن نتوقف
That's it!
!ذاك
Hey! Stop, you kids!
!أنتم! توقفوا يا أطفال
Stop the car! Or else I'll do this!
!أوقف السيّارة! وإلّا سأفعل هذا
Damn kids!
!الصبيّ اللعين
Who were those kids?!
!من كان أولئك الصغار؟
Hell if I know!
!لا أعرف
Let's just hurry! There's no time!
!لنسرع بأيّ حال! لا وقت لدينا
Ugh! My hands are going numb!
...تبّاً، يداي تتخدران
I can't hold on any longer!
...لا يمكنني الصمود
Genta!
غينتا
Ayumi! Ayumi! Ayumi!
!أيومي! أيومي! أيومي
It's those kids!
!إنّهم أولئك الأطفال
Who cares?! Let's just get her out of there and split!
!لا تهتم لهم! لنخرجها فقط وننفصل
Right!
!أ-أجل
Who're you?!
!من أنت؟
Who is this brat?!
!من هذه الطفلة؟
What?!
!ماذا؟
Ayumi!
!أيومي
Here goes!
حسنٌ
Hey, be quiet!
!ا-اصمتي
Ayumi!
!اهربي يا أيومي
Get down!
!خُذ
Ayumi-chan!
!أيومي-تشان
You're all here!
!رفاق
I'm so glad you're all right!
!حمداً لله لكونك بخير
You had us worried!
!جعلتنا نقلق
It's all over for you!
انتهى أمركم
You're the ones who've been kidnapping and murdering little girls!
!يا مختطفا وقاتلا الفتيات
Murdering?!
!قاتلا؟
There's no point in playing dumb!
!لا فائدة من التحامق
We heard your guys' conversation in the car!
!سمعنا محادثتكم في السيّارة
Yeah! You said you'd have no trouble killing little kids!
!صحيح! قلت أنّ لا مشكلة لديك في قتل الأطفال
And then there's the corpse and money in your trunk!
كما هناك الجثّة والمال في صندوق سيارتكما
Try talking your way out of that one!
لا مهرب لكما
You idiots!
!حـ-حمقى
Take a better look!
!أمعنوا النظر
They're all hand-made props!
!كلّها معدات مصنوعة
Props?!
معدات؟
Our conversation in the car was us practicing our lines one last time!
محادثتنا في السيارة كانت تدريباً !على حوارنا للمرّة الأخيرة
Practicing your lines?
تدريباً على حواركم؟
We're performing in a play here!
!نحن نؤدي مسرحيةً هنا
Come to think of it!
...تذكرت
Let's go to Teitan University's school festival, Conan-kun!
لنذهب لمهرجان جامعة تيتان يا كونان-كن
I hear they're going to have an interesting mystery play!
!سمعت أنّهم سيؤدون مسرحية تحرٍّ مثيرة
And besides, they said on the radio that they just caught the murderer!
!كما قالوا على الراديو أنّهم أمسكوا بالمجرمين
Inspector Megure!
مفتّش ميغوري؟
So was that the real killer then?
...كان ذاك القاتل الحقيقي إذاً
Look at what you've done!
!انظروا لما فعلتم
He has a big lump and a broken neck!
...به نتوء كبير وعنقه مكسور
Well, it was nice meeting you...
...سنغادر إذاً
Not so fast!
!توقفوا
Yes?
أ-أجل؟
You'll have to take responsibility for this!
!ستتحملون المسؤولية
Her parents paid the r... ransom,
لن نعيش لنرى الغد
and besides, she's just a kid...
كما أنّها مجرد طفلة
You fool! She's seen our faces!
!أحمق! رأت وجهينا
We can't leave her alive!
!لا يمكننا تركها حيّة
Hey, there's something weird about that actor.
هناك خطبٌ ما بذاك الممثل
You think?
تظنين ذلك؟
He can't stand up straight, and he keeps blowing his lines!
لا يمكنه الوقوف منتظماً، ويخفق في ترديد كلمات حواره
No thanks...
...كـ-كلا، شكراً
Oh, come on, now! Wouldn't you like to see my famous detective skills--
لا تقولي هذا! ألا تريدين رؤية مهارات ...التحرّي الشهيرة لي
That's enough of that!
!يكفي
Genta! Say the next line!
!غينتا! قُل الجملة التالية
I don't know how to read this word!
لا أعرف كيف أقرأ هذه الكلمة
That's right--we were put onstage
صحيح، لعبنا دور شخصية رئيسية
That's pronounced "cruel"!
"تُنطق "قاسٍ
as a main character.
على المسرح
That's cruel!
!هذا قاسٍ
Incidentally, the role of the decapitated head...
...كما أنّ دور الرأس المقطوع
...went to Ayumi-chan herself.
كان لأيومي-تشان نفسها
I hate Hide-and-Go-Seek!
!أكره الغميضة
He's dead?!
!بعدما وجدت أباها أخيراً... يا للفظاعة
There's still no saying for sure that he was murdered...
لا يمكننا الجزم بأنه قُتل بعد
We can't give up yet!
!بسرعة! لأصل في الوقت
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The Bizarre Manhunt Murder.
جريمة قتل تقصّي رجل الغريبة
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
A Hundred Million Yen.
مئة مليون ين